♪ Oh, if there was a problem,
you can't solve it ♪
♪ Check out the hook
while my DJ revolves it ♪
♪ Ice, Ice, baby ♪
(Priya (off):)Oh, God, I feel
ridiculous in this dress.
(Leonard(off):)You look beautiful,
Lieutenant Uhura.
(Leonard(off):)Now prepare for... inspection.
(Priya(off):)Shh, my brother's
going to hear you.
(Leonard(off):)Relax, he's got
headphones on.
(Leonard(off):)And we're ten miles above
Earth in a starship.
(Raj:)Really, ten miles?
(Raj:)You're orbiting inside
the atmosphere?
(Raj:)Moron.
(Priya(off):)I can't believe
I'm wearing
(Priya(off):)my brother's Halloween costume.
(Leonard(off):)I can't believe you think
he only wears it on Halloween.
(Leonard(off):)Open the landing bay doors,
shuttle craft approaching.
(Raj:)Okay, gotta go.